In this video we will know
how much salary do you get in ICICI Lombard as an
insurance advisor, this is the post of advisor,
how much salary will you get in such a long company,
we will talk in detail in this post,
before the butter, if you are not on the channel, do
subscribe, this video is fine,
friends, Mithun YouTube channel where
you get job vacancies updates, so if
you want any development, please subscribe to
Sumit Jain,
go to Delhi and give me the link in the description box to get any update
[music]
Soft Sangh, here details of ICICI Lombard company,
talk about everything, celebs do
not understand this, you do
not have to pay attention to this, let's talk about
basic to
100 medical sciences,
Rupesh Karanvir WhatsApp, Aero Sperm
Android, so friends, you should click on the
subscribe button, you will get 1000 from the total salary, you should subscribe to the
advisor in the company, you have to subscribe to
them,
you have 3220 subscribers here, do it for
10 minutes  You
can earn from ₹50 to ₹90, if you have been instructed
then salary will come in your fund account
but you will get
salary of ₹1604 in your account, S8
salary in hand salary in and the post of
advisor in ICC Loot company, send SMS
that you have friends, simple graduates
get jobs, right soft will be on this post, if you liked the
video, then
like and subscribe, thank you for
watching this video.